ILGWU. Research Department wages and hours files, 5780/148
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ILGWU Research Department - Brief on Behalf of the ILGWU in the Matter of the Re-examination by Special Industry Committee Number 5 for Puerto Rico of Minimum Wage Rates Established by Wage Orders for Puerto Rico Under the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  July 11
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Special Industry Committee for Puerto Rico, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special industry Committee Number 7, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Hearing Before Special Industry Committee, Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Special Industries Committee for Puerto Rico, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Public Hearing Before Special Industries Committee Number 3. Puerto Rico, April 11-13
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 8, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Public Hearings For the Leather, Leathergoods, and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 9
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 8, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Public hearings for the Handicrafts Product Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 10
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 8, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Public Hearings for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Industry. Exhibit of Administrator Number 1. Volume 12.
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22A, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Public Hearing for Fabric and Leather Glove Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Special Industry Committee Number 19B, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Public Hearing for the Textile and Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22A, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for Fabric and Leather Glove Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 20A, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 6
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22A, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Public Hearing for Fabric and Leather Glove Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 5
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22A, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Public Hearing for Fabric and Leather Glove Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 4
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22A, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Public Hearing for Fabric and Leather Glove Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22B, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 22B, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22A, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Public Hearing for Fabric and Leather Glove Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Recommendations, Decisions, and Wage Order. Volume 6
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22B, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 22D, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Public Hearing for Women's and Children's Underwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 22C, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Public Hearing for Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Recommendations, Decisions, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22B, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Recommendations, Decisions, and Wage Order. Volume 4
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 19A, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Exhibits, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 51
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Public Hearing for the Needlework and Fabricated Textiles Industry (Administrator's Exhibits), Volume 15
- U.S. Wage and Hours and Public Contracts Division, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  In the Matter of the Minimum Wage Recommendations for the Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Number 15, Volume 1. Pages 1-210
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 20A, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 3. Pages 320-423
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 20A, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2. Pages 204-319
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 20A, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Appointment and Hearings. Volume. Pages 1-203
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 17A, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Hearing in the Matter of the Minimum Wage Recommendation of Special Industry Committee. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 18A, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Exhibits, Volume 4
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Appointment of Committee and Notices of Hearings, Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 19A, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Public Hearing for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 3. pages 509-805
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 19A, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Public Hearing for the Corset, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico, Volume 2. Pages 218-508
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 19A, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Public Hearing for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 1, Pages 1-217
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 17A, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Public Hearings. Exhibits and Statements. Volume 4
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 17A, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Exhibits and Statements, Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 17A, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Public Hearing for Silk, Rayon, and Nylon Underwear Division and the General Division of the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 1. Pages 1-86
- U.S. Wages and Hour and Public Contracts Division Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Hearing in the Matter of the Minimum Wage Recommendation in the Needlework Industry. Exhibits and Oral Argument. Volume 27
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Hearing in the Matter of the Minimum Wage Recommendation for Men's and Boys' Clothing. Exhibits and Statements, Oral Argument, and Orders. Volume 26
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 20, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 4. Pages 424-562
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Industry Committee Number 15, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Hearings in the Matter of the Minimum Wage Recommendation in the Needlework Industry. Findings, Opinion, Briefs, and Wage Order. Volume 28
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 20A, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 5. Pages 563-758
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Public Hearings for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry. Volume 5. Pages 1140-1466
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Public Hearings for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry. Volume 6. Pages 1469-1823
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for the Needlework and Fabricated Textiles Industry. Exhibits and Statements. Volume 6
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Public Hearing for the Corset, Brassieres, and Allied Garment Industry. Exhibit and Statements. Volume 14
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Public Hearing for the Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry. Volume 3, Pages 601-790
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Public Hearing for the Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry. Exhibits and Statements. Volume 17
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry. Volume 2. Pages 254-600.
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Hearings in the Matter of the Minimum Wage Recommendations for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 1. Pages 1-133
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  In the Matter of Minimum Wage Recommendations for the Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 2. Pages 211-413
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  The Minimum Wage Recommendation for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry. Volume 18
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Hearings in the Matter of the Minimum Wage Recommendations for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 2. Pages 134-323
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Abstracts of Testimony, Volume 29
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  Hearings in the Matter of Minimum Wage Recommendations for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 3. Pages 324-478
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Hearing in the Matter of the Minimum Wage Recommendation for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments. Exhibits, Statements, Oral Argument, and Orders. Volume 25
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Hearing in the Matter of Minimum Wage Recommendations for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry. Volume 4. Pages 479-710
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 38B, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 1. Pages 1-295
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31C, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Public Hearing for Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing. Volume 1. Pages 1-360
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 30A, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for Corset, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22E, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Public Hearing Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2. Pages 336-659
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22E, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Recommendations, Decisions, and Wage Order. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22E, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1. Page 1-335
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22C, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Public Hearing for Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 22D, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Public Hearing for Women's and Children's Underwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Recommendations, Decisions, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 38A, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Public Hearing for Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31E, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Public Hearing for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31D, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2. Pages 178-407
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 38A, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Public Hearing for Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Public Hearings for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry. Volume 7. Pages 1824-1994
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Public Hearings for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry. Volume 4. Pages 795-1139
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry. Volume 3. Pages 579-794
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Public Hearing for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry. Volume 2. Pages 261-578
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Public Hearing for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry. Volume 1. Pages 1-260
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Public Hearing for the Corset, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry. Volume 2. Pages 256-511
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Public Hearing for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garment Industry. Volume 1. Pages 1-255
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 9, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Public Hearing for the Handkerchief, Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Minimum Wage Recommendation of Special Industry Committee Number 8 for Puerto Rico for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Committee Number 8, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Public Hearings for the Establishment of Minimum Wage Rates in the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 17
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 8, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Public Hearings for the Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits and Statements. Volume 16
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 8, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Public Hearing for the Leather, Leather Goods, and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits and Statements. Volume 15.
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 8, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  Public Hearings for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits and Statements. Volume 14
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 8, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  Public Hearings for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits and Statements. Volume 8
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 8, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  Public Hearings for the Men's and Boy's Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 6
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 15, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related products Industry. Volume 1. Pages 1-253
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 38B, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 2. Pages 296-579
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee 40A, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 1, July
- U.S. Wage and hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 40B, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse and Neckwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 1, July
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31A, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2. Pages 306-586
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 30B, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2. Pages 328-656
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 30B, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1. Pages 1-327
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31B, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Public Hearing for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse and Neckwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2. Pages 237-621
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31B, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Public Hearing for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse and Neckwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1. Pages 1-236
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31A, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1. pages 1-305
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31D, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1. Pages 1-177
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 38B, 1956-1958 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boy's Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31A, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, Wage Order. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 30B, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 30A, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for Corset, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31B, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Public Hearing for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse and Neckwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31E, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Public Hearing for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 31C, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Public Hearing for Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 48C, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Public Hearings for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse and Neckwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 40C, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Public Hearing for Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 40B, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Public Hearing for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse and Neckwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 40E, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Public Hearing for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 3